Finding Aid for Engineering Communications & Marketing (University of Michigan) records 1860-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan 1998
- Visual Material (2010 Accession)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets and Negatives
    - Other (1980-2010)
      - Individuals A-Z
        - Goff Smith, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Kenneth Snelson (Sculptor)/ Indexer II Sculpture, 1999 (Box 20)
        - Rick Snyder, 2001 (Box 20)
        - Gary Talbot, 2/24/2003 (Box 20)
        - Helen (ne Benz) & Theodore R. Thoren 31E, December 2003 (Box 20)
        - Catherine and Ame Vennema (Box 20)
        - Dean Charles Vest, 1990 (Box 20)
        - Robert J. Vlasic, 1997 (Box 20)
        - Father Williams, 7/1/2001 (Box 20)
        - Terry G. Wood, 9/1/1991 (Box 20)
        - Shien-Ming "Sam" Wu, 9/12/1991 (Box 20)
        - Zili Wu (MSE), 10/7/1993 (Box 20)
        - Jingxia Yuan (MEAM), 9/1/1995 (Box 20)
        - National Advisory Committee (NAC) Members as of 1990-1991 Frederick Beer, Robert Frosch, Robert Fuhrman, Samuel Irwin, Ray Judson, Kaye Lathrop, Georges Skurla, Raymond Smit, Jerome Smith, Irving G. Snyder, Jr. William Streett, Robert Tuttle, Late, 1980s-1990 (Box 20)
        - NAC Members as of 1992-1993 Frederick Buckman, Donald Frey, Sam Fuller, Ken Kohrs, Early, 1990s (Box 20)
        - NAC Members, Retired as of-1992-93-Joseph Boyd, William Brown, Dwight Carlson, Chris Dingell, Herbert (Ted) Doan, Robert Eaton, Kenneth Kohrs, Craig Marks, George Nersesian, Benson Shapiro, William Sommers, John Weil, 1992-3 (Box 20)
        - NAC Members 1994 H. Adams, C.M. Armstrong, C. Arrison, C. Atkisson, Jr., K. Baker, M.D. Baldwin Ii, J. Breen, G. Brunner, C. Charles, P. Coleman, Jr., K. Crain, S. Frey, D. Graham, J. Grettenberger, J. Guglielmi, R. Heglin, T. Hodgson, J. Holt, P. Jacobi, R. Kerber, K. Kohrs, J. Kreick, Bernard Lacroute, J. Levin, David Liddle, R. Lutz, S. Maslak, J. McDivitt, J. McTague, J. Mellor, A. Mika, S. Rabinowitz, R. Reins, J. Rowe, D. Runkle, B. Schuette, R. Sheldon, J. Stronge, R. Teeter, J. Ullrich, J. Utley, J. Warner, P. Weinberger, I. Wilson, 1994 (Box 20)
        - National Advisory Committee (NAC) New Members 1995/W. David Tarver, Larry Potter, Heinz Prechter, Don Defosset Gloria Jeff, Robert Paster (Box 20)
        - NAC Directory/Richard Auhll ('00), K. Baker (00), E. Baum (01), R. Cooper (00), R. Crandall (99), D. Graham (00), P. Gray (01), J. Hall, T. Herrick (99), J. Holt (99), P. Jacobi (99), Sangtae Kim (01), K. Kohrs (01), J. Kreick (00), J. Levin (99), D. Liddle (00), R. Lutz (00), J. Mctague (99), Joel Moses (00), R. Paster (01), L. Potter (01), R. Reins (99), D. Rothwell (00), W. Showalter (00), B. Schuette (99), R. Snyder (01), J. Spira (99), T. Stephens (01), W. David Tarver (98), R. Teeter (99), R. J. Utley (99), J. Warner (00), P. Yhouse (01), 1998-99 (Box 20)
        - NAC/Robt Buckler '02; L. Burns '02; Don Defosset '01, Robt Kramek '02; Tim Leuliette '02, Les Loomans Ex Officio; Robt Lutz '00; W. Rhines '02; Doug Rothwell '00, W. Schowalter '00; John Warner '00, 1999-2000 (Box 20)
        - NAC Directory 2000-2001 Mark Baker/ Lawrence Burns/ M. Eskew/ M. Korybalski/ Doug Rothwell/ R. Scott/ Peter Staudhammer/ Charla Wise (Box 20)
        - NAC Members W/ unknown Years-John Betti, John Seely Brown, Dan Drucker, Robt. Graham, Richard McCord, Milton Meckler, Fred Merer, Warren Miller Jr., Kenneth Pickar, Percy Pierre, Doug Ross, Wesley Wheeler (Box 20)
        - Kedrick Adkins, Summer 2001 (Box 21)
        - Rick Snyder, Summer 2001 (Box 21)
        - Chris Theodore, Summer 2001 (Box 21)
        - Sangtae Kim, Summer 2001 (Box 21)
        - AERO/ (NASA Group) Students, 1992 (Box 21)
        - Students at ELRC, Fall 1990 (Box 21)
        - Students with Prof. Ken Wise (J. Lund), 10/5/1992 (Box 21)
        - CRLT, John Everett, 3/20/1992 (Box 21)
        - UMEC President Brad Finkbeiner, 1998 (Box 21)
        - UMEC President Chitra Laxmanan 3/20/2003 (Box 21)
        - Luther Mitchell UMEC President, 2005 (Box 21)
        - Hopwood Award Winners '93/Students, 1993 (Box 21)
        - Detroit Space Grant Program-Students (Box 21)
      - Student Activities
        - AERO Zero Gravity Program/Vomit Comet, March 2000 (Box 21)
        - Design Expo, 12/5/1996 (Box 21)
        - Engineering Students on Football Team, 9/18/2003 (Box 21)
        - Students Summer Traveling (Box 21)
        - Student Shots-Off Campus Activities, unknown (Box 21)
        - Classroom/Student Shots, 10/16/2002 (Box 21)
        - Global Engineering Class Party, 2002; 4/16/2002 (Box 21)
        - Engineering Senior Picnic, 4/12/2001 (Box 21)
        - Career fair, 10/7/1996 (Box 21)
        - Human Powered Submarine 8 and 9, 2001; June 2001 (Box 21)
        - Engineering Welcome Day, 2002; 8/30/2002 (Box 21)
        - Engineering Welcome Day, 9/5/2000 (Box 21)
        - Solar Car race, Summer 2001; 7/1/2001 (Box 21)
        - World Solar Challenge 2001 Australia, 11/2001 (Box 21)
        - Welcome Day, 2001; 09/04/2001 (Box 21)
        - Camp CAEN, Summer 1997 (Box 21)
        - Autoshow, Solar Car, 1/10/2003 (Box 21)
        - Solar Car Race, July 25, 2001 (Box 21)
        - Springfest '97 and UMEC President Kim Dillon, 1997 (Box 21)
        - Springfest, 2001; 4/17/2001 (Box 21)
        - Springfest, 2000; 4/14/2000 (Box 21)
      - Student Services (Box 22)
        - Engineering Career Fair, 2001; 9/25/2001 (Box 22)
        - Minority Student Society Reception/SMES, 4/22/1999 (Box 22)
        - Sea Classroom & Student Expo Shots, 7/7/1997 (Box 22)
        - Miscellaneous student shots, fountain, wave field, IOE hallway, September 2002 (Box 22)
        - Honda Civic Hybrid, 10/2002 (Box 22)
        - Minority Summer Program MEPO, 2001 (Box 22)
        - Student Honors Brunch, 3/18/2001 (Box 22)
        - Ford Summer Engineering Institute Dedication (SEI, MEPO), 7/11/2003 (Box 22)
        - Student Leadership Dinner, 3/17/2001 (Box 22)
      - Women in Engineering
        - WISE Summer Program / Hot Air Balloon, 6/23/1999 (Box 22)
      - Departments
        - Biomed FMRI, October 2002 (Box 22)
        - EECS Hologram, 8/25/2003 (Box 22)
        - EEECS Instructional Computer Lab (Room 4440)/ Intel Computers, 1/27/2000 (Box 22)
        - ME: Noel Perkins, Fly-Fishing, 2/3/2010 (Box 22)
        - ME Research-Vegetable Based Cutting Fluids/M, 8/26/2003 (Box 22)
        - ME/ Global Product Design Class, 11/9/2000 (Box 22)
        - MEAM/ Carmel/ Prof. Yoram Koren, 10/1/1988 (Box 22)
        - ME/Global Product Realization Course, 12/8/2000 (Box 22)
        - NAME/ M-Rover, 2/1/1994 (Box 22)
        - NAME / Drafting Room, 6/21/1988 (Box 22)
        - NERS Energy and the Environment Symposium, Joseph Knollenberg, 10/4/2002 (Box 22)
        - NERS/ Intense Energy Beam Interaction Lab (Box 22)
        - Co-Op Brochure Photos, 1994 (Box 22)
- Faculty Background Files
  The Faculty Background Files (ca. 1980 -- ca. 2000, 12 linear feet) series consist of photographs, curriculum vitae, profiles, and news clippings of Engineering faculty from the early 1980s to the late 1990s. Each faculty member is identified by their departmental association, some of which are different than the College's current department names. The acronyms used are identified as:
  AERO - Aerospace Engineering
  AOSS - Atmospheric, Oceanic and Space Sciences
  BiomedE - Biomedical Engineering
  Chem - Chemical Engineering
  CEE - Civil and Environmental Engineering
  EECS - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science
  IOE - Industrial and Operations Engineering
  MSE - Materials Science and Engineering
  MEAM - Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics
  NAME - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering
  NERS - Nuclear Engineering and Radiological Sciences
  SPRL -- Space Physics Research Laboratory
  - Vincent J. Abreu (AOSS) (Box 23)
  - Linda M. Abriola (CEE) (Box 23)
  - Mimi Adams (Tech. Comm.) (Box 23)
  - Thomas C. Adamson, Jr. (AERO) (Box 23)
  - Peter Adriaens (CEE) (Box 23)
  - Rajendra Aggarwala (CEE) (Box 23)
  - A. Ziya Akcasu (NERS) (Box 23)
  - Rayhaneh Akhavan (MEAM) (Box 23)
  - George Albercook (AOSS) (Box 23)
  - Herbert H. Alvord (MEAM) (Box 23)
  - Achilleas Anastasopoulos (EECS) (Box 23)
  - David J. Anderson (EECS) (Box 23)
  - William J. Anderson (AERO) (Box 23)
  - Charles J. Antonelli (EECS) (Box 23)
  - John M. Armstrong (CEE) (Box 23)
  - Thomas Armstrong (IOE) (Box 23)
  - Vedat S. Arpaci (MEAM) (Box 23)
  - Ellen M. Arruda (MEAM) (Box 23)
  - James A. Ashton-Miller (MEAM) (Box 23)
  - Dennis N. Assanis (MEAM) (Box 23)
  - Daniel E. Atkins (EECS) (Box 23)
  - Arvind Atreya (MEAM) (Box 23)
  - Sushil K. Atreya (AOSS) (Box 23)
  - Michael Atzmon (NERS) (Box 23)
  - Eric M. Aupperle (EECS) (Box 23)
  - Todd Austin (EECS) (Box 23)
  - Dennis G. Baker (AOSS) (Box 23)
  - Gilda E. Ballester (AOSS) (Box 23)
  - James R. Barber (MEAM) (Box 23)
  - Michael J. Barcelona (CEE) (Box 23)
  - John R. Barker (AOSS) (Box 23)
  - Andrei L. Barkovskii (CEE) (Box 23)
  - Frederick L. Bartman (AOSS) (Box 23)
  - Ben F. Barton (EECS) (Box 23)
  - Marthalee S. Barton (Tech. Comm.) (Box 23)
  - Rainer Bauske (AOSS) (Box 23)
  - James C. Bean (IOE) (Box 23)
  - Gorman Beauchamp (Humanities) (Box 23)
  - Robert F. Beck (NAME) (Box 23)
  - Klaus-Peter Beier (NAME) (Box 23)
  - Dmitry Beletsky (NAME) (Box 23)
  - Spencer L. Bement (EECS) (Box 23)
  - Harry B. Benford (NAME) (Box 23)
  - Glen V. Berg (CEE) (Box 23)
  - Ronald Berliner (NERS) (Box 23)
  - Luis P. Bernal (AERO) (Box 23)
  - Michael M. Bernitsas (NAME) (Box 23)
  - Dennis S. Bernstein (AERO) (Box 23)
  - Frederick J. Beutler (EECS, AERO) (Box 23)
  - Satinder Singh Beveja (EECS) (Box 23)
  - Pallab K. Bhattacharya (EECS) (Box 23)
  - Alex F. Bielajew (NERS) (Box 23)
  - Wilbur C. Bigelow (MSE) (Box 23)
  - Stacy G. Bike (Chem.) (Box 24)
  - John C. Bilello (MSE) (Box 24)
  - Kurt C. Binder (MEAM) (Box 24)
  - Theodore G. Birdsall (EECS) (Box 24)
  - William P. Birmingham (EECS) (Box 24)
  - Ofer Blum (Chem.) (Box 24)
  - Jay A. Bolt (MEAM) (Box 24)
  - Seth Bonder (IOE) (Box 24)
  - Johann Borenstein (MEAM) (Box 24)
  - Claus Borgnakke (MEAM) (Box 24)
  - Stephen Bougher (AOSS) (Box 24)
  - Iain D. Boyd (AERO) (Box 24)
  - John P. Boyd (AOSS) (Box 24)
  - Yavuz A. Bozer (IOE) (Box 24)
  - Larry H. Brace (AOSS) (Box 24)
  - Mary L. Brake (NERS) (Box 24)
  - Ernest F. Brater (CEE) (Box 24)
  - Mark Brehob (EECS) (Box 24)
  - Diann Erbschloe Brei (MEAM) (Box 24)
  - Dale E. Briggs (Chem.) (Box 24)
  - Susan V. Brooks (BiomedE) (Box 24)
  - Richard B. Brown (EECS) (Box 24)
  - William M. Brown (EECS) (Box 24)
  - Jonathan W. Bulkley (CEE) (Box 24)
  - Joseph L. Bull (BiomedE) (Box 24)
  - Howard M. Bunch (NAME) (Box 24)
  - Harm Buning (AERO) (Box 24)
  - Arthur W. Burks (EECS) (Box 24)
  - Alan G. Burns (AOSS) (Box 24)
  - Mark A. Burns (SPRL) (Box 24)
  - Jeremy Busby (NERS) (Box 24)
  - Charles A. Cain (EECS) (Box 24)
  - Donald A. Calahan (EECS) (Box 24)
  - Raymond P. Canale (CEE) (Box 24)
  - John J. Carey (IOE) (Box 24)
  - George R. Carignan (AOSS; SPRL). (Box 24)
  - Brice Carnahan (Chem.) (Box 24)
  - Robert I. Carr (CEE) (Box 24)
  - Mary Anne Carroll (AOSS) (Box 24)
  - Paul L. Carson (BiomedE) (Box 24)
  - Matthew P. Castanier (MEAM) (Box 24)
  - Steven L. Ceccio (MEAM) (Box 24)
  - Dariusz J. Ceglarek (MEAM) (Box 24)
  - Carlos Cesnik (AERO) (Box 24)
  - Don B. Chaffin (IOE) (Box 24)
  - Zenghu Chang (EECS) (Box 25)
  - Kan Chen (EECS) (Box 25)
  - Peter M. Chen (EECS) (Box 25)
  - Stephen E. Chick (IOE) (Box 25)
  - Wooyoung Choi (NERS) (Box 25)
  - Kuei Chuang (EECS) (Box 25)
  - John A. Clark (MEAM) (Box 25)
  - Samuel K. Clark (MEAM) (Box 25)
  - John T. Clarke (AOSS) (Box 25)
  - C. Robert Clauer (AOSS) (Box 25)
  - Donald E. Cleveland (CEE) (Box 25)
  - John T. Coffey (EECS) (Box 25)
  - Richard J. Coffey (IOE) (Box 25)
  - Hubert I. Cohen (Humanities) (Box 25)
  - Amy Cohn (IOE) (Box 25)
  - David E. Cole (MEAM) (Box 25)
  - Kevin R. Collins (CEE) (Box 25)
  - Michael R. Combi (AOSS) (Box 25)
  - Maria Comninou (MEAM) (Box 25)
  - Kevin J. Compton (EECS) (Box 25)
  - Lynn Conway (EECS) (Box 25)
  - Donald N. Cortright (CEE) (Box 25)
  - Aline J. Cotel (CEE) (Box 25)
  - Selden Crary (EECS) (Box 25)
  - Andrew Crawford (IOE) (Box 25)
  - Rane L. Curl (Chem.) (Box 25)
  - Werner J. A. Dahm (AERO) (Box 25)
  - Jason M. Daida (AOSS) (Box 25)
  - Amelio M. D'Arcangelo (NAME) (Box 25)
  - Joseph Datsko (MEAM) (Box 25)
  - Edward S. Davidson (EECS) (Box 25)
  - Walter R. Debler (MEAM) (Box 25)
  - Avery H. Demond (CEE) (Box 25)
  - Robert G. Dennis (BiomedE) (Box 25)
  - Darren Dezeeuw (AOSS) (Box 25)
  - William B. Dickens (Humanities) (Box 25)
  - Robert B. DiGiovanni (Tech. Comm.) (Box 25)
  - A. Nelson Dingle (AOSS) (Box 25)
  - Stephen W. Director (EECS) (Box 25)
  - M. Craig Dobson (EECS) (Box 25)
  - Francis M. Donahue (Chem.) (Box 25)
  - David R. Dowling (MEAM) (Box 25)
  - Paul Drake (AOSS) (Box 26)
  - S. Roland Drayson (AOSS) (Box 26)
  - James F. Driscoll (AERO) (Box 26)
  - James J. Duderstadt (NERS), 3 folders (Box 26)
  - Edmund H. Durfee (EECS) (Box 26)
  - Debasish Dutta (MEAM) (Box 26)
  - Jack R. East (EECS) (Box 26)
  - Heribert Eisele (EECS) (Box 26)
  - Joe G. Eisley (AERO) (Box 26)
  - Sherif El-Tawil (CEE) (Box 26)
  - Stanislav Emelianov (BiomedE) (Box 26)
  - Anthony W. England (EECS) (Box 26)
  - John H. Enns (MEAM) (Box 26)
  - Marina Epelman (IOE) (Box 26)
  - Bogdan Epureanu (MEAM) (Box 26)
  - Laurel Erickson (Tech. Comm.) (Box 26)
  - Robert D. Ervin (MEAM) (Box 26)
  - Gary Evans (CEE) (Box 26)
  - David Everest (MEAM) (Box 26)
  - John G. Everett (CEE) (Box 26)
  - Rodney C. Ewing (NERS) (Box 26)
  - Michael Falk (MSE) (Box 26)
  - Jiasong Fang (CEE) (Box 26)
  - Hansford W. Farris (EECS) (Box 26)
  - John A. Faulkner (BiomedE) (Box 26)
  - David K. Felbeck (MEAM) (Box 26)
  - Jeffrey A. Fessler (EECS) (Box 26)
  - Robert Scott Fijan (MEAM) (Box 26)
  - Zoran S. Filipi (MEAM) (Box 26)
  - Frank E. Filisko (MSE) (Box 26)
  - Jack A. Fishstrom (Tech. Comm.) (Box 26)
  - Lennard A. Fisk (AOSS) (Box 26)
  - Sebastion Fixson (IOE) (Box 26)
  - Ronald F. Fleming (NERS) (Box 26)
  - Jason Flinn (EECS) (Box 26)
  - Michael J. Flynn (NERS) (Box 26)
  - H. Scott Fogler (Chem.) (Box 26)
  - Ernest G. Fontheim (SPRL) (Box 26)
  - Ann Ford (EECS) (Box 26)
  - James Foulke (IOE) (Box 26)
  - J. Brian Fowlkes (BiomedE) (Box 26)
  - James S. Freudenberg (EECS) (Box 26)
  - Peretz Peter Friedmann (AERO) (Box 26)
  - David L. Galbraith (NERS) (Box 27)
  - Alec D. Gallimore (AERO) (Box 27)
  - Almantas Galvanauskas (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Krishnakumar Garikipati (MEAM) (Box 27)
  - Donald E. Geister (AERO, MEAM) (Box 27)
  - Ward D. Getty (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Amit K. Ghosh (MSE) (Box 27)
  - Ronald Gibala (MSE) (Box 27)
  - Elmer G. Gilbert (AERO) (Box 27)
  - Brian E. Gilchrist (AOSS, EECS) (Box 27)
  - Ronald M. Gilgenbach (NAME) (Box 27)
  - Brent Gillespie (MEAM) (Box 27)
  - Thomas D. Gillespie (MEAM) (Box 27)
  - John L. Gland (Chem.) (Box 27)
  - D. Roger Glass (AERO) (Box 27)
  - Sharron Glotzer (Chem.) (Box 27)
  - Eugene A. Glysson (CEE) (Box 27)
  - Subhash C. Goel (CEE) (Box 27)
  - Rachel S. Goldman (MSE) (Box 27)
  - Steven A. Goldstein (MEAM) (Box 27)
  - Tamas Gombosi (AOSS) (Box 27)
  - Pierre Goovaerts (CEE) (Box 27)
  - Donald H. Gray (CEE) (Box 27)
  - Daniel G. Green (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Paul A. Green (IOE) (Box 27)
  - Donald T. Greenwood (AERO) (Box 27)
  - Dennis Grimard (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Jessy W. Grizzle (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Karl Grosh (MEAM) (Box 27)
  - Jim Grotberg (BiomedE) (Box 27)
  - Erdogan Gulari (Chem.) (Box 27)
  - Lingjie Jay Guo (EECS) (Box 27)
  - George I. Haddad (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Mehrdad Haghi (MEAM) (Box 27)
  - Merrick Haller (CILER) (Box 27)
  - John W. Halloran (MSE) (Box 27)
  - Walton M. Hancock (IOE) (Box 27)
  - Will Hansen (CEE) (Box 27)
  - Robert D. Hanson (CEE) (Box 27)
  - Jon Harris (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Robert B. Harris (CEE) (Box 27)
  - Walt Harris (AOSS) (Box 27)
  - John P. Hayes (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Kim F. Hayes (CEE) (Box 27)
  - Paul B. Hays (AOSS, AERO) (Box 27)
  - Zhong He (NERS) (Box 27)
  - Shane Henderson (IOE) (Box 27)
  - Luis Hernandez (BiomedE) (Box 27)
  - Alfred O. Hero III (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Gary D. Herrin (IOE) (Box 27)
  - Bertram Herzog (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Michael Herzog (AOSS) (Box 27)
  - Robert L. Hess (MEAM) (Box 27)
  - Jamille Hetke (EECS) (Box 27)
  - Eric Hildinger (Tech. Comm.) (Box 27)
  - Robert H. Hoisington (MEAM) (Box 28)
  - Warne C. Holcombe (Humanities) (Box 28)
  - John H. Holland (EECS) (Box 28)
  - Scott J. Hollister (MEAM) (Box 28)
  - James Paul Holloway (NERS) (Box 28)
  - Peter Honeyman (EECS) (Box 28)
  - William F. Hosford, Jr. (MSE) (Box 28)
  - Robert M. Howe (AERO) (Box 28)
  - Roman D. Hryciw (CEE) (Box 28)
  - Shixin (Jack) Hu (MEAM) (Box 28)
  - Edward E. Hucke (MSE) (Box 28)
  - Jane E. Huggins (BiomedE) (Box 28)
  - David Y. Hughes (Humanities) (Box 28)
  - Richard Hughes (BiomedE) (Box 28)
  - Gregory M. Hulbert (MEAM) (Box 28)
  - Alan Hunt (BiomedE) (Box 28)
  - Charles J. Hurbis (CEE) (Box 28)
  - David Charles Hyland (AERO) (Box 28)
  - Hong Im (MEAM) (Box 28)
  - Photios G. Ioannou (CEE) (Box 28)
  - Keki Irani (EECS) (Box 28)
  - Mohammed N. Islam (EECS) (Box 28)
  - Stanley J. Jacobs (AOSS, MEAM) (Box 28)
  - H.V. Jagadish (EECS) (Box 28)
  - Farnam Jahanian (EECS) (Box 28)
  - Janice M. Jenkins (EECS) (Box 28)
  - Jionghua, Jin (IOE) (Box 28)
  - Thomas Johengen (CILER) (Box 28)
  - Rod Johnson (Tech. Comm.) (Box 28)
  - J. Wayne Jones (MSE) (Box 28)
  - Tibor Juhasz (BiomedE) (Box 28)
  - Pierre T. Kabamba (AERO) (Box 28)
  - Robert H. Kadlec (Chem.) (Box 28)
  - Julie Kafkalidis (AOSS) (Box 28)
  - Movses J. Kaldjian (CEE, NAME) (Box 28)
  - Vineet Kamat (CEE) (Box 28)
  - Terry Kammash (NERS) (Box 28)
  - Jerzy Kanicki (EECS) (Box 28)
  - Elijah Kannatey-Asibu (MEAM) (Box 28)
  - Barry Kantowitz (IOE, U-M Transportation Research Institute) (Box 28)
  - Stephen Kaplan (EECS) (Box 28)
  - Bruce H. Karnopp (MEAM) (Box 28)
  - Dale Karr (NAME) (Box 28)
  - Linda P.B. Katehi (EECS) (Box 28)
  - Nikolaos D. Katopodes (CEE) (Box 28)
  - Katsuo Kurabayashi (MEAM) (Box 28)
  - C. William Kauffman (AERO) (Box 28)
  - Massoud Kaviany (MEAM) (Box 28)
  - Kimberlee J. Kearfott (NERS) (Box 29)
  - Gerald J. Keeler (AOSS) (Box 29)
  - Robert B. Keller (MEAM) (Box 29)
  - William Kerr (NERS) (Box 29)
  - W. Monroe Keyserling (IOE) (Box 29)
  - Pramod P. Khargonekar (EECS) (Box 29)
  - David E. Kieras (EECS, IOE, Tech. Comm.) (Box 29)
  - Noboru Kikuchi (MEAM) (Box 29)
  - Daryl Kipke (BiomedE) (Box 29)
  - John S. King (NERS) (Box 29)
  - Peter R. Klaver (Tech. Comm.) (Box 29)
  - Karl Kluge (EECS) (Box 29)
  - Glenn F. Knoll (NERS) (Box 29)
  - Yuan-Kuen Ko (AOSS) (Box 29)
  - Muammer Koc (MEAM) (Box 29)
  - Daniel E. Koditschek (EECS) (Box 29)
  - David H. Kohn (BiomedE) (Box 29)
  - Yoram Koren (MEAM) (Box 29)
  - Sridhar Kota (MEAM) (Box 29)
  - Janet U. Kozyra (AOSS) (Box 29)
  - Costas Kravaris (Chem.) (Box 29)
  - William R. Kuhn (AOSS) (Box 29)
  - Arthur D. Kuo (MEAM) (Box 29)
  - Edward R. Lady (MEAM) (Box 29)
  - Stphane Lafortune (EECS) (Box 29)
  - Richard Mason Laine (MSE) (Box 29)
  - John Laird (EECS) (Box 29)
  - Thomas Lamb (NAME) (Box 29)
  - Edward Larsen (Chem.) (Box 29)
  - Ronald G. Larson (NERS) (Box 29)
  - Yue-Ying Lau (NERS) (Box 29)
  - John C. Lee (NERS) (Box 29)
  - Sheryl Leicher (Tech. Comm.) (Box 29)
  - Emmett N. Leith (EECS) (Box 29)
  - William C. Leslie (MSE) (Box 29)
  - Simon Levine (BiomedE) (Box 29)
  - Mark Lewis (IOE) (Box 29)
  - Victor C. Li (CEE) (Box 29)
  - Ruth Lieberman (AOSS) (Box 29)
  - Michael W. Liemohn (AOSS) (Box 29)
  - Valdis V. Liepa (EECS) (Box 29)
  - Jeffrey Liker (IOE) (Box 29)
  - Liwei Lin (MEAM) (Box 29)
  - Jennifer J. Linderman (Chem.) (Box 29)
  - Vadim Linetsky (IOE) (Box 29)
  - Robert A. Lionberger (Chem.) (Box 29)
  - Mingyan Liu (EECS) (Box 29)
  - Vi-Cheng Liu (AERO) (Box 29)
  - Yili Liu (IOE) (Box 29)
  - Ronald J. Lomax (EECS) (Box 29)
  - Ralph A. Loomis (Humanities) (Box 30)
  - Wei Lu (MEAM) (Box 30)
  - Kenneth C. Ludema (MEAM) (Box 30)
  - Jonathan E. Luntz (MEAM) (Box 30)
  - David R. Lyzenga (NAME) (Box 30)
  - Peter X. Ma (BiomedE) (Box 30)
  - Zheng-Dong Ma (MEAM) (Box 30)
  - Michel Maharbiz (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Richard K. Mains (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Anatoly M. Maksimchuk (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Scott Mahlke (EECS) (Box 30)
  - John F. Mansfield (MSE) (Box 30)
  - Igor Markov (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Lee Markosian (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Craig Marks (IOE) (Box 30)
  - Frank Marsik (AOSS) (Box 30)
  - Bernard J. Martin (IOE) (Box 30)
  - David C. Martin (MSE) (Box 30)
  - Sandrine Martin (EECS) (Box 30)
  - William R. Martin (NERS) (Box 30)
  - J. C. Mathes (Tech. Comm.) (Box 30)
  - Carlos Mastrangelo (MEAM) (Box 30)
  - Jyotirmoy Mazumder (MEAM) (Box 30)
  - Pinaki Mazumder (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Glenn H. Mazur (IOE) (Box 30)
  - Leo C. McAfee, Jr. (EECS) (Box 30)
  - N. Harris McClamroch (AERO), EECS) (Box 30)
  - Patrick J. McCleer (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Colleen McGee (Tech. Comm.) (Box 30)
  - Doug McGregor (NERS) (Box 30)
  - Charles W. McMullen (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Guy A. Meadows (AOSS, NAME) (Box 30)
  - Semyon M. Meerkov (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Mostafa Mehrabi (MEAM) (Box 30)
  - Herman Merte, Jr. (MEAM) (Box 30)
  - Arthur F. Messiter, Jr. (AERO) (Box 30)
  - Kurt Metzger (EECS) (Box 30)
  - John F. Meyer (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Radoslaw L Michalowski (CEE) (Box 30)
  - Nestor F. Michelena (MEAM) (Box 30)
  - Eric Michielssen (EECS) (Box 30)
  - James M. Miller (IOE) (Box 30)
  - Joanna Mirecki Millunchick (MSE) (Box 30)
  - Susan M. Montgomery (Chem.) (Box 30)
  - David James Mooney (Chem.) (Box 30)
  - Andrew Morgan (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Zissimos P. Mourelatos (NAME) (Box 30)
  - Grard Albert Mourou (EECS) (Box 30)
  - James R. Moyne (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Trevor N. Mudge (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Srilata Mukherjee (Tech. Comm.) (Box 30)
  - Katta G. Murty (IOE) (Box 30)
  - Mary Ann Mycek (BiomedE) (Box 30)
  - Antoine E. Naaman (CEE) (Box 30)
  - Andrew F. Nagy (AOSS, and EECS) (Box 30)
  - Vijayan N. Nair (IOE) (Box 30)
  - Khalil Najafi (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Adib Nashashibi (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Arch W. Naylor (EECS) (Box 30)
  - John Nees (EECS) (Box 30)
  - Torsten Neubert (AOSS) (Box 31)
  - David L. Neuhoff (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Clark T.C. Nguyen (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Jun Ni (MEAM) (Box 31)
  - J. Arthur Nicholls (AERO) (Box 31)
  - Rick Niciejewski (AOSS) (Box 31)
  - Brian Noble (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Richard C. Nolen-Hoeksema (CEE) (Box 31)
  - Douglas C. Noll (BiomedE) (Box 31)
  - Theodore B. Norris (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Andrzej S. Nowak (CEE) (Box 31)
  - Okey Nwogu (NAME) (Box 31)
  - Matthew O'Donnell (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Leslie A. Olsen (Tech. Comm.) (Box 31)
  - Tava Lennon Olsen (IOE) (Box 31)
  - Terese Olsen (CEE) (Box 31)
  - Andrejs Olte (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Nicolae Orlandea (MEAM) (Box 31)
  - Gilbert Oswald (Tech. Comm.) (Box 31)
  - Clyde L. Owings (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Tuba zkan-Haller (NAME) (Box 31)
  - Jwo Pan (MEAM) (Box 31)
  - Xiaoqing Pan (MSE) (Box 31)
  - Stella W. Pang (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Marios C. Papaefthymiou (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Panos Y. Papalambros (MEAM) (Box 31)
  - Vladimir O. Papitashvili (AOSS) (Box 31)
  - Euisu Park (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Gustavo Parra-Montesinos (CEE) (Box 31)
  - Michael G. Parsons (NAME) (Box 31)
  - Zbigniew Pasek (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Jignesh Patel (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Donald J. Patterson (MEAM) (Box 31)
  - Dimitris Pavlidis (EECS) (Box 31)
  - J. Raymond Pearson (MEAM) (Box 31)
  - Robert D. Pehlke (MSE) (Box 31)
  - Huei Peng (MEAM) (Box 31)
  - Joyce E. Penner (AOSS) (Box 31)
  - Anastassios N. Perakis (NAME) (Box 31)
  - Noel C. Perkins (MEAM) (Box 31)
  - Marc Perlin (NAME) (Box 31)
  - Lauren Peterson (EECS) (Box 31)